Guide to the American Baptist Foreign Mission Society records, 1813-1961
American Baptist Foreign Mission Society records, 1813-1961
- Series II. Subject file--Burma
  - Burma-Pwo Karen ? History of Pwo Karen Work, 1911-1937 (Reel 704-4-14)
  - Burma-Lahu/Wa ? Kengtung: Report of Survey Comm 3/19/06 (Reel 704-4-15)
  - Burma-Kachin ? Tribes & Dialects. O. Hanson 1907 (Reel 704-4-16)
  - Burma-Kachin ? Pioneering among the Kachins. W.H. Roberts, 1911 (Reel 704-4-17)
  - Burma ? Kachin ? Myitkyina, 1912-1933 (Reel 704-4-18)
  - Burma ? Kachin ? Bhamo, 1917-1938 (Reel 704-18)
  - Burma ? Kachin ? Missionary Progress. O. Hansen, 1922 (Reel 704-5-1)
  - Burma ? Kachin ? Miscellaneous, 1923-1941 (Reel 705-1-1)
  - Burma ? Kachin ? The Triangle, 11/1/26 (Reel 705-1-2)
  - Burma ? Kachin ? The Jubilee, 1927 (Reel 705-1-3)
  - Burma ? Kachin ? Sumprabum, 1936-1941 (Reel 705-1-4)
  - Burma ? Kachin, Kutkai & Nampaka, 1938-1949 (Reel 705-1-5)
  - Burma ? Kachin, Mission to the Kachins. The work of G.A. Sword, 1941 (Reel 705-1-6)
  - Burma ? All Karen. Karen Baptist Convention ? Sgaw Karen Bible Centenary, 1853-1953 (Reel 705-1-7)
  - Burma ? All Karen ? Karen Folk Lore. An unwritten Bible. Ko San Lone, 1913 (Reel 705-2-1)
  - Burma ? All Karen. Karen Women?s Mission Society. 1920-1941 (Reel 705-2-2)
  - Burma ? All Karen-Bassein Ko Tha Byu High school. 1923-1941 (Reel 705-2-3)
  - Burma ? All Karen. Ko Tha Byu Karen Centenary ? Tavoy 1928-1929 (Reel 705-2-4)
  - Burma ? All Karen. On the threshold of the Century 1828-1928 Harry & Emma Marshall. 1929 (Reel 705-2-5)
  - Burma ? All Karen. Baptist Missionary Review 1/19/29 (Reel 705-2-6)
  - Burma ? All Karen. The Karen Mission in Burma. Emma Marshall, 1931 (Reel 705-2-7)
  - Burma ? All Karen. Historical (Reel 705-2-8)
  - Burma ? Sgaw Karen-Tavoy, 1844-1940 (Reel 705-3-1)
  - Burma ? Sgaw Karen ? Shwegyin, 1902-1938 (Reel 705-3-2)
  - Burma ? Sgaw Karen ? Nyanglebin, 1922-1940 (Reel 705-3-3)
  - Burma ? Kahu/Wa Controversy re: Williams Young?s work, 1907-1919 (Reel 705-3-4)
  - Burma ? Lahu/Wa ? Bana, Mong Yang, 1925-1942 (Reel 705-3-5)
  - Burma ? Lahu/Wa - Mong Mong Stations, 1925-1942 (Reel 705-3-6)
  - Burma ? Lahu/Wa ? Traditions of the Lahus, 1929-1941 (Reel 705-3-7)
  - Burma ? Lahu/Wa ? Mong Mong Bana Mission, Yunau Province, Difficulties with Chinese Government, 1930-1934 (Reel 705-3-8)
  - Burma ? Mons-Mon Work, 1896-1956 (Reel 705-4-1)
  - Burma ? Shan ? Kentung, 1905-1941 (Reel 705-4-2)
  - Burma-Shans - General, 1907-1936 (Reel 705-4-3)
  - Burma-Shans ? Mongnai area, Shan States 1917-1941 (Reel 705-4-4)
  - Burma-Shans, History of Kentung Mission, 1927 (Reel 705-4-5)
  - Burma ? Tribal Group, Taunggyi Area, Multilingual 1905-1955 (Reel 705-4-6)
  - Burma - Tribal groups - Lisus, Kaws (Ahkas) 1919-1955 (Reel 705-4-7)
  - Burma ? Tribal groups ? Katinni State Red Karens, Padaungs, etc. 1931-1939 (Reel 705-4-8)
  - Burma ? Tribal groups ? Black Karens, Striped Karens, etc. 1936-1940 (Reel 705-4-9)
  - Burma ? Burma Christian Council ? General Mat. 1931-1945 (Reel 705-4-10)
  - Burma - Burma Christian Council - Oxford Group, 1935-1936 (Reel 705-4-11)
  - Burma ? Burma Christian Council - Pamphlets (Reel 705-4-12)
  - Burma ? Education ? Survey. Relation of Schools and Higher Education to Missionary operations Vol. 1, Jan-Oct. 1893 (Reel 706-1-1)
  - Burma ? Education ? Survey. Relation of Schools and Higher Education to Missionary Operation. Vol. 2, Nov. 1893-94 (Reel 706-1-2)
  - Burma ? Education. Education Grants in Aid, 1912 (Reel 706-1-3)
  - Burma ? education ? Scheme for Tenasserim School Industrial and Mechanical trades in Moulmein, Burma, 1918-1924 (Reel 706-1-4)
  - Burma ? Education ? Education in Burma & Baptist Principles. Smith, 1920 (Reel 706-1-5)
  - Burma ? education ? General material, 1920-1929 (Reel 706-1-6)
  - Burma ? education ? General material, 1930-1939 (Reel 706-2-1)
  - Burma ? Schools. Mandalay: Boy's High School. 1934-1945 (Reel 706-2-2)
  - Burma ? Schools. Mandalay: Girls' High School, 1924-1940 (Reel 706-2-3)
  - Burma ? Schools. Maymyo Girls' School (Colgate) 1925-1941 (Reel 706-2-4)
  - Burma ? Schools. Moulmein, Daingwaunkwin, Karen High School, 1925-1941 (Reel 706-2-5)
  - Burma ? Schools. Moulmein: English Girls' High School, 1915-1942 (Reel 706-2-6)
  - Burma ? Schools. Moulmein: Judson Boys' High Sch. 1919-1920 (Reel 706-2-7)
  - Burma ? Schools. Moulmein: Morton Land Girls' High Sch. 1923-1941 (Reel 706-2-8)
  - Burma ? Schools. Rangoon: Baptist English High School, 1921 (Reel 706-3-1)
  - Burma ? Schools. Rangoon. Baptist college, 1907-1915 (Reel 706-3-2)
  - Burma ? Schools. Rangoon: Baptist Normal School, pamphlets (Reel 706-3-3)
  - Burma ? Schools. Rangoon: Cushing High School. Coles Memorial clock Tower, 1917-1933 (Reel 706-3-4)
  - Burma ? Schools. Kemmendine Girls' High School. 1900-1942 (Reel 706-4-1)
  - Burma ? Schools. Taunggyi: Huldah Mix Girls' School, 1926-1942 (Reel 706-4-2)
  - Burma ? Schools. Taunggyi: School for Missionaries children (Reel 706-4-3)
  - Burma ? Schools. Byinmana Agricultural school. General material 1917-1942 (Reel 706-4-4)
  - Burma ? Schools. Pyinmana Gricultural School. Teports 1922-1941 (Reel 707-1-1)
  - Burma ? Schools. Pyinmana Agricultural School. Lena Tillman Case Home Crafts School, 1937-1941 (Reel 707-1-2)
  - Burma ? Schools. Pyinmana Agricultural School. General Material 1942-58 (Reel 707-1-3)
  - Burma ? Schools. Pyinmana Agricultural School. Pamphlets (Reel 707-1-4)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College Annual Reports 1902-1919 (Reel 707-2-1)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College Annual Reports, 1922-1930 (Reel 707-2-2)
  - Burma - Schools. Judson College Annual Reports, 1930-1935 (Reel 707-2-3)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College Annual Reports, 1935-1941 (Reel 707-2-4)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College Constitutions, 1927-1940 (Reel 708-1-1)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College, Lindsay Comm Report, 1931 (Reel 708-1-2)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College. Historical Acct. 1899-1937 (Reel 708-1-3)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College, 1915-1922 (Reel 708-1-4)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College, 1923 (Reel 708-1-5)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College, 1924 (Reel 708-1-6)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College 1925 (Reel 708-1-7)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College 1926 (Reel 708-1-8)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson college 1927 (Reel 708-1-9)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College, Benton Hall 1927-1930 (Reel 708-1-10)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College 1928 (Reel 708-1-11)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College 1929 (Reel 708-1-12)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College 1931 (Reel 708-1-13)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College 1932 (Reel 708-1-14)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College 1933 (Reel 708-1-15)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College 1934 (Reel 708-1-16)
  - Burma. Schools. Judson College 1935 (Reel 708-1-17)
  - Burma. Schools. Judson college 1936 (Reel 708-1-18)
  - Burma ?Schools. Judson College 1937 (Reel 708-2-1)
  - Burma ?Schools. Judson College 1938 (Reel 708-2-2)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College 1930 (Reel 708-2-3)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College 1939 (Reel 708-2-4)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College 1940 (Reel 708-2-5)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College 1941 (Reel 708-2-6)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College 1942 (Reel 708-2-7)
  - Burma ?Schools. Judson College 1943 (Reel 708-2-8)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College 1944 (Reel 708-2-9)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College 1945 (Reel 708-2-10)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College 1947 (Reel 708-2-11)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College 1948 (Reel 708-2-12)
  - Burma ? Schools. Judson College Pamphlets (Reel 709-1-1)
  - Burma ? Theological Education, General 1930 (Reel 709-2-1)
  - Burma ? Theological Education. Theological Training 1931 (Reel 709-2-2)
  - Burma ?Theological Education. Pwo Karen Bible School, Rangoon. Pwo Karen Bible Training School 1877-1948 (Reel 709-2-3)
  - Burma ? Theological Education. Burman Theological Seminary 1899-1940 (Reel 709-2-4)
  - Burma ? Theological Education. Karen Women?s Bible School Rangoon & Insein: Karen Women?s Bible School 1897-1947 (Reel 709-2-5)
  - Burma ? Theological Education. Baptist Divinity School. General Material 1934-1941 (Reel 709-2-6)
  - Burma ? Theological Education. Karen Theol. Sem. Insein. Karen Theological seminary, 1883-1941 (Reel 709-3-1)
  - Burma ? Theological Education. Burman Women?s Bible School, Insein. Burman Women?s Bible School, 1922-1941 (Reel 709-3-2)
  - Burma ? Medical. Susan Haswell Leper Home, 1900-1950 (Reel 710-1-1)
  - Burma ? Medical. Kengtung: Louise Hastings Memorial Hospital and Leper work, 1915-1940 (Reel 710-1-2)
  - Burma ? Medical. Namkham, 1915-1951 (Reel 710-1-3)
  - Burma ? Medical. Moulmein. Christian Hospital ? Ellen Mitchel Memorial 1921-1941 (Reel 710-1-4)
  - Burma ? Medical. Leper work, 1922-1941 (Reel 710-1-5)
  - Burma ? Medical. Taunggyi: Peabody Montgomery Rest Haven 1934-42 (Reel 710-1-6)
  - Burma ? Medical. Medical missionary work. Dr. A.H. Henderson, 1924 (Reel 710-1-7)
  - Burma ? Medical. Namkham Hospital, 1927-1947 (Reel 710-1-8)
  - Burma ? Medical. Namkham Hospital, 1948-1956 (Reel 710-2-1)
  - Burma ? Medical. Namkham Hospital, 1958-1964 (Reel 711-1-1)
  - Burma ? Medical. Moulmein Hospital History. Anna M. Barkley (Reel 711-1-2)
  - Burma ? Medical. Medical work policy. (Reel 711-1-3)
  - Burma ? Mission Press. Press inventory, 1882 (Reel 711-1-4)
  - Burma ? Mission Press. Mission press reports, 1902-1912 (Reel 711-1-5)
  - Burma ? Mission Press. Mission press reports, 1912-1919 (Reel 711-1-6)
  - Burma ? Mission Press. Press accounts, 1920-1930 (Reel 711-2-1)
  - Burma ? Mission Press. Attack on Prof. & Mrs. Paul Gleason 10/24 (Reel 711-2-2)
  - Burma ? Mission Press. Report by G.B. Huntington, 1927 (Reel 711-2-3)
  - Burma ? Mission Press ? Correspondence & Minutes, 1928-1946 (Reel 711-2-4)
  - Burma ? Mission Press. Misc. correspondence 1934-1945 (Reel 711-2-5)
  - Burma ? Mission Press. Correspondence about sale of press, 1936-40 (Reel 711-2-6)
  - Burma ? Mission Press. Policy, 1941 (Reel 711-3-1)
  - Burma ? Mission Press. The Remington Burmese typewriter (Reel 712-1-1)
  - Burma ? Mission Press. History of press (Reel 712-1-2)
  - Burma ? Mission Press. Pamphlets (Reel 712-1-3)